Izzy: Hey, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Hi.
Izzy: Is that the new Sony?
Ben: What?
Oh…yeah, it is.
Izzy: Cool.
This is a great camera!
Ben: Um…
Izzy: Can I take a photo?
Ben: Uh…Sure…
Izzy: Not here.
Outside.
Come on!
Ben: Is my bag OK here?
Thank you.
Wait…wait!
Izzy: I love this camera.
You’re American, right?
Ben: Yeah, I am.
But my dad’s from Mexico.
Izzy: Where are you from in the US?
Ben: I’m from California.
From a very small town.
Izzy: What do you think of London?
Ben: It’s nice.
I like it.
Izzy: Are you on holiday?
Ben: No. I’m a student.
Izzy: Where?
Ben: At the Tensquare School of Photography.
I start on Thursday.
Izzy: Tired?
Ben: I’m very tired.
Izzy: Come with me.
Come on.
Let’s go.
This is my favourite park.
Ben: It’s…perfect!
Thank you.
Izzy: You’re welcome.
Sorry.
Work.
Time to go.
Bye, Mr Fischer.
Ben: Ben…My name’s Ben…Wait, what’s your name?